好的  过来  别偷看
Okay. Come on, no peeking.
我们闭上眼睛了  然后穿过大街  太好了
Our eyes are closed, and we're about to cross the street. Very good.
好  可以睁开了
Okay. Open up.
你要让我们看什么  因为我们看到的只有辆棒极了的货车
What did you want to show us? Because all I can see is this bitchen van.
这是我们备办伙食用的
Yeah, it's for our catering business.
我想我见过那女孩
Oh. I think I know that girl.
好吧  我们不会一直让它那样的  什么
All right, umm, we're not gonna really keep it this way though. No?
我们会用棍子面包代替那把剑
We're gonna paint over the sword and replace it with a baguette.
噢
Oh.
还有这个也不知道要怎么处理
And also, we don't know what to do with this.
想起来了  我肯定见过她
Oh, yeah, I definitely know her.
老友记  第四季  第09集  参加派对
Friends S04E09  The one where they're gonna party
（主演：詹妮弗·安妮斯顿）
（主演：柯特妮·考克斯）
（主演：丽莎·库卓）
（主演：马特·勒布朗）
（主演：马修·派瑞）
（主演：大卫·修蒙）
还记得我跟你说过的  那个在厨艺学校时别管做什么都放芫荽叶的那人
Remember that guy from cooking school I told you about that put cilantro with everything?
记得  当然  芫荽赖瑞嘛
Oh, sure, Cilantro Larry.
我是《切尔西报道》被他选定的食评家
Well, I'm gonna fill in for him as food critic for the Chelsea Reporter.
哇  摩妮卡  大好机会啊  你能影响到
Wow. Monica, what an amazing opportunity to influence
几十号人了
...dozens of people.
你同意了  那我们的承包伙食生意怎么办
How could you say yes, What about our catering business?
噢  不要紧的  只是每周一晚
Oh, no, no, it's just one night a week.
而且我还可以带你们大家去吃免费晚餐
and plus I get to take all of you out for a lot of free dinners.
啊  噢
Hey. Oh.
既然是那样的话  耶
Oh, in that case—Yay!
刚才是我跳上车一起去
That was me hopping onboard. Oh.
嘿  大伙儿好  嘿  罗斯  快问快答
Hey, guys. Hey, Ross. Quick question for you.
准备好狂欢没有
Are you ready to party?
没有  出去喝几杯啤酒或许可以
I don't know, I could maybe go out for a couple of beers.
但我打算看探索频道的"大黄蜂"节目
But there's this thing about bumblebees on the Discovery Channel.
不  不 我想你没听清楚我说什么  准备好狂欢没有
No, no, no, I don't think you heard me. Are you ready to party?
不会吧
No.
甘道夫   甘道夫要来吗
Gandalf? Gandalf is coming to town?
凯西要陪她父母  而我就没事可干了
Kathy's with her parents, I have nothing to do.
所以明天我们要跟甘道夫去狂欢  花花公子
so tomorrow we are partying with Gandolf dude!
花花公子  我们要去狂欢了
Dude, we are so gonna party. Yeah.
好了  花花公子们注意
Wow, okay. Dude alert.
这个人是谁
And who is this guy?
麦克甘道夫  甘德森  世上超有趣的家伙
Mike "Gandalf" Ganderson. Only, like, the funnest guy in the world.
我得打电话  明天请假
I'm gonna call and get off work tomorrow.
你打完我也请假
Oh. I'm gonna call after you.
兄弟  这一定超酷的  我们八百年没狂欢了
This is gonna be so cool. Dude, we never party anymore.
喔  喔
Whoo! Whoo!
你们是不是躲在我们车里  偷抽了大麻
All right, were you guys smoking something in the back of our van?
是啊  什么叫八百年没狂欢  跟我在一起就很快乐啊
Really. And what do you mean you never have fun anymore? You have fun with me.
记不记得那次看脱衣舞  你给我50美元要我吞书
Remember the time we saw those strippers and you paid me 50 bucks to eat that book?
乔伊  你会喜爱这个人的  就像是"舞会魔法师"
Joey, you are gonna love this guy. Gandalf is like the party wizard.
你们干嘛叫他"甘道夫"   魔法师甘道夫啊
Well, why do you call him Gandalf? Gandalf the wizard.
喂  你高中难道没看过"指环王"吗
Hello? Didn't you read Lord of the Rings in high school?
没有  但我高中上过床来着
No, I had sex in high school.
喔  乔安娜  能不能请教你一点事
Oh. Uh, Joanna? I was wondering if I could ask you something.
淑女服饰的采购助理有空缺
There's an opening for an assistant buyer in Junior Miss
那我岂不是连降三级了
Okay, but that would actually be a big step down for me.
不是啦  事实上  我是说我挺合适的
No, actually, I meant for me.
招聘委员会每天都在面试
The hiring committee is meeting people all day and...
我很希望我能拒绝  但我总不能让你当我一辈子的助理吧
Oh. Well, I wish I could say no, but I guess you can't stay my assistant forever.
苏菲  你不能去  但不是这个理由
Neither can you, Sophie, but for different reasons.
天那  我真高兴你这么宽容大量
God, I'm so glad you don't have a problem with this.
因为如果你有意见  我根本就不会去报名了
because if you did, I wouldn't even consider applying.
真的啊  那样的话
Really? Well, in that case
我非常高兴你同意了  没什么问题了
And that's why I'm so glad there's no problem.
那好吧  其实我也是招聘委员会的一员  你去起码能看到一张熟面孔
That's fine, actually I'm on the hiring committee, so there'll be at least one friendly face.
噢  太好了
Oh, that's great.
你知道  我也是从淑女部干起的
You know, Junior Miss is where I started.
噢  那时为了得到那份工作  不得不跟最丑的男人上床
I had to sleep with the ugliest guy to get that job.
真的啊  才不呢
Really? No. Ha, ha.
是真的
Yeah.
我是说  假的啦
I mean, no. No, no, no. Ha, ha. No. Ha, ha.
别担心  我可以肯定  以你的资历  不用跟男人上床也能得到这份工作
don't you worry, I'm sure with your qualifications you won't need to sleep with some guy to get that job.
虽然我对此并不十分信服
Although, uh, I might need some convincing.
哦  我  开玩笑的
Um... Oh. Kidding. Ha, ha.
天啊  我今天还真有点兴奋
God, I feel wild today. Aah!
要命  哥们  我太激动了  兴奋的都快吐了
Oh, man, I am so excited, I may vomit.
能不能冷静点  他不过是个普通人而已
Will you calm down? He's just a human guy.
你不明白的  甘道夫超神的
Look, you don't understand. Gandalf is amazing.
你将无法知道下一步将发生什么
Y'know you're never know what's gonna end up happening,
你开始只不过是跟他去喝两杯   醒来竟然正在坐渔船去加拿大
You go out for a couple of beers and end up on a fishing boat to Nova Scotia.
真的  对  那里风景很美
Really? Oh, yeah, it's beautiful country up there.
嘿  好
Hey. Okay.
我拿了护照  干净袜子  还有蛇毒解药
I got my passport, fresh socks, and a snakebite kit.
这次不会跟上次一样又到那去的
It's not gonna be exactly like last time.
好吧  伙计们  回头见
All right, I'll see you guys.
喔  喔  喔
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
我有一个试听课  晚点再跟你们会合
I have an audition, but I'll definitely hook up with you later.
你们中午左右会在哪里
Where you gonna be around noon? Heh.
差不多在赤道附近吧
Somewhere maybe along the equator?
好
Okay.
喂
Hello?
甘道夫打来的
It's Gandalf.
你到了么
So are you in town?
喔  这样啊…
Oh, well...
那就下次再约吧
Well, maybe next time, then.
怎么了
What happened?
他在芝加哥被耽搁了  没办法来
He's not gonna make it. He's stuck in Chicago.
要命
Oh, man.
芝加哥  真是太走运了
Chicago, is sooo lucky!
我还蠢得去换了这些加拿大元币
Stupid, useless Canadian money.
葛林小姐  你的工作经历还不错
You have a very impressive resume, Ms. Green.
我认为您这里提到的文件归档系统非常棒
I especially like what I see here about implementing a new filing system.
谢谢
Thank you.
文件归档系统  就是你弄在文件夹上那些彩色标签
Filing system? Oh, you mean those-those little colored labels you put on all the folders?
那倒是的确给档案柜增色不少
It certainly did brighten up the inside of the filing cabinets.
标签的作用不止于此
Well, they, uh... they-they did more than that.
我看到你肩负了许多重要职责
I notice that you've been entrusted with a lot of important responsibilities.
对  乔安娜确实对我有知遇之恩
Yes. Joanna really has been an incredible mentor to me.
瑞秋每天早上给我送百吉饼  做得也非常不错
Oh. And Rachel has been really incredible at getting my morning bagel.
不可思议  她几乎每次都不会买错
It's amazing how she gets it right almost every time.
我  我  我当然  还有其他更多的职责
I-I-I of course, I have more responsibilities than that.
没错  还有咖啡也是  瑞秋一次能拎两样东西
Oh, yes, of course. There's the coffee too. Rachel can carry two things at once.
相当优秀
That's, uh, very good.
现在这个工作的很大一部分
Now a uh, a big part of this job...
是建立同他人的关系  特别是和设计师
...is cultivating personal relationships, especially with designers.
对  我意识到… 这点瑞秋没问题
Yes, Yes, I realize that... Rachel shouldn't have any problem with that.
唯一的问题就是怕她打得太火热  如果你们知道我说的
Her only problem might be getting a little too friendly, if you know what I mean.
我最喜欢和设计师共事了
I love working with designers.
共事或共枕  又有什么差别呢  瑞秋
With them, under them, what's the difference, eh, Rach?
我第一篇美食评论上报了  哦  《切尔西报道》
Hey. My first review is out. Oh! Oh, the Chelsea Reporter, ohh,
以前我都拿它来盖在身上御寒
Ah. These used to keep me so warm.
快看  我的评论在反面
All right, look at my on the back page. Ooh. Oh!
好   "我还会再去光顾亚历山卓吗  当然  但我会点两份餐
Okay. "Would I go back to Allesandro's? Sure, but I would have to order two meals.
一份给我   一份给那个用枪指着我的头逼我再到这个餐厅的人"
One for me, and one for the guy pointing the gun to my head."
哇  你真把这家店批得一文不值
Wow, you really laid into this place.
报社付我钱  又不是要我广结朋友
Hey, they don't pay me a penny a word to make friends.
我得走了  我找到一个人  他可以修咱们外面的货车
Ooh, I gotta go. I found a guy who could fix up the van for catering.
要不要我跟你一块去  不用  没事
Oh. Do you need me to go with you? No, no, it's okay.
但你确定我们不要那张水床了么
But are we sure we don't want the waterbed?
我们不是早就说好了  对啦
Haven't we made this decision? Yeah.
再见  再见
Bye. Bye.
谁啊
Who is it?
我是亚历山卓餐厅的老板
It's Allesandro, from Allesandro's.
天啊
Oh, my God.
我想跟你谈谈你的那篇评论  哦  天啊  天啊
I wanna talk to you about your review. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
你打电话给我
Call me on the phone.
为什么  那样你可以随时挂掉电话
Why? So you could hang up on me?
我不会让你上来的  你还是走吧
But I'm never gonna let you up, so you may as well just go away.
给我个机会
Just give me a chance to...
你要进去么  来吧
Hey, Do you need to get in? Here you go.
菲比  不行啦  嗨  摩妮卡
No, Phoebe! Oh, hey, Monica.
我要你收回你的评论  我们的食物绝非"难以下咽"
I want a retraction. Our food is not "inedible swill."
我就吃不下去
I couldn't eat it.
我那五个朋友也难以下咽  虽然他们中的一个连书都能吃
I have five friends who couldn't eat it, and one of them eats books.
那么  至少我们的服务  也不是"宾至如衰"
Well, our service is not "grossly incompetent."
你们的服务员把面包棒塞在裤子里
The waiter carried the breadsticks in his pants.
你还写  我们店里接受发现卡
Well, you said that we accept the Discover Card
其实不行
which we do not.
好啊  那句话我可以收回
All right, that I'll retract.
但我坚持我的观点  我懂美食  但决不是你们那样
But I stand by my review. I know food, and that wasn't it.
你们的意式沙拉  尝起来就像是番茄汁
Your marinara sauce tastes like tomato juice.
你们应该加些伏特加酒与芹菜末
You should serve it with vodka and a piece of celery.
我以店里那果汁为荣  很美味
Hey, I'm proud of that sauce. It's delicious.
天啊
Oh, my God.
你是开意大利餐厅的  竟然认为那样很美味
You own an Italian restaurant and you think that tastes good?
你从哪来的
Where are you even from?
黎巴嫩
Lebanon.
把那些蕃茄递给我
Hand me those tomatoes.
我来示范纯正的味道是怎样来的  给我
I'm gonna show you what it should taste like. Come on.
你要弄多久啊  我还要去骂另一个美食评论家
How long is this gonna take? 'Cause I got another critic I gotta go yell at.
乔安娜  我想跟你谈谈面试的事
Ahem. Uh, Joanna, I wanna talk about that interview.
我觉得你的面试不错啊
I thought it went very well.
不  它很差  我就是要跟你说这件事
No, it didn't. That's what I wanna talk to you about.
现在  简单点说
Now, just to brief you
我可能会哭出来
I may cry.
并不是因为伤心和生气
But they are not tears of sadness or of anger
而是因为我要你跟讨论这件事
but just of me having this discussion with you.
瑞秋  请不要这样
Rachel, please, don't make a scene.
这里又没人
There's nobody here.
苏菲  你进来
Sophie, get in here.
看吧  你让苏菲尴尬了
You see? Now you're making Sophie uncomfortable.
我没有尴尬啊
She's not making me uncomfortable.
恭喜  你总算有点作用了  出去
Congratulations, You now just crossed the line into completely useless. Get out.
你是要我辞职吗
Do you want me to quit?
什么  你怎么会这样想
What? What would make you think that?
因为那些你在面试时说的话
Well, all of those things you said in the interview.
如果里面有你的真心话  那我一定不是个好助理
I mean If you believe any of them, I must not be a very good assistant.
不如这样吧
You know what?
我收拾下办公桌
I am just going to pack up my desk
今天下班后就走人
and I will be gone by the end of the day.
我想没必要耗到今天下班了
Well, I guess there's no use me sticking around till the end of the day.
你等等…
Wait, wait, wait.
把那可怜的小松糕放回抽屉里
You can put your sad little muffin back in its drawer.
如果你要听实话的话  我不想失去你这完美的助理
If you must know the truth, I didn't wanna lose a perfectly good assistant.
什么
What?
所以我才瞎掰出你轻浮和酗酒的事
That's why I said all those things about your flirting and your drinking.
我酗酒
My drinking?
那我一定是在你离开后说的
Oh. I must have said that after you left.
你到底说了什么
Said what, exactly?
你时不时喜欢酗酒...
That you enjoyed the occasional drink...
酒后乱性
...ing binge.
天啊  够了  我得离开这
Oh, my God. Oh. That is it. I'm leaving.
你太可怕了  不要  等等
You are just a horrible person. No, wait, wait, wait.
如果你真的在意这个职位的话
Now, if you're gonna get all sensitive about it.
我真不想失去你
I don't want to lose you.
不如  我给你创造这么个职位怎样
What if I create a position for you?
我让你在这部门里  担任采购助理
I'll make you assistant buyer in this department.
再多说一点
Say more things like that. Um...
你有自己独立的办公室  外带加薪  明天就生效
You can have your own office and a raise, effective tomorrow.
我需要公费报销  没问题
I'd need an expense account. Done.
还要有助理  苏菲  进来
And an assistant. Sophie, get in here.
嘿  你们怎么在这里
Hey, what are you guys doing here?
我以为你们和甘到夫狂欢了
I thought you'd be partying with Gandoldorf.
是甘道夫  他不来了
It's Gandalf, and he's not coming.
那你们一早都呆坐在这里  没有
So you've been sitting here all morning? No.
我刚刚把帐算好了
I balanced my checkbook.
对  我给所有的足球桌里的小人都起了名字
Yeah, and I gave first names to all the foosball players.
不敢相信甘道夫竟然没来
I can't believe he didn't come.
他不来又怎样  我们还是可以自己出去狂欢啊
So what if he didn't come? We can still go out and party ourselves.
哦  不  有甘道夫在  我们一整晚都有的玩的
Oh, no, you know, with Gandalf, we'd be out all night.
而且还能和一堆陌生人一起混  跟他们待在外面不回来
Yeah, we'd meet total strangers and hang out with them.
我们也可以啊
Well, we can do that.
他还有其他的绝招
There was other stuff too.
我们都会啊  而且更好
We'll do it all, and better.
瞧着吧  今晚过后  就换我们带甘道夫去狂欢  兄弟们
Look, after tonight, Gandalf will wanna party with us, dude.
来吧
Come on.
对  对
Yeah. Yeah.
好像我们不会狂欢似的  好了么  我们走
It's not like we don't know how to party. Yeah. All right. Let's go.
最后再到一次船上如何
And may-maybe we could end up on a boat again?
好耶
Yeah! All right!
哈
Ah!
嘿  嘿  嘿  什么时候  什么时候咱们在船上
Hey-hey-hey, when uh, when were we on a boat?
记得那天早上很冷
Remember that really cold morning
你醒来发现那些“狗”在舔你的脸
you woke up and those dogs were licking your face?
记得  老兄  舔你的是那些海豹
Yeah. those were seals, man.
摩妮卡  问你个小问题  采购助理穿这套装如何
Hey Mon, little question for ya! How do you think this suit will look on an assistant buyer?
亚历山卓的老板上门来吼我
Okay, the owner of Allesandro's came over to yell at me,
但我趁机做了些沙拉给他  结果他就雇我当他的首席大厨
but instead I made him some sauce, and he offered me the job as head chef!!
天啊
Oh, my God.
你毁了我在回家路上练了好久的好戏  但我真是替你高兴
You just ruined the thing I was practicing the whole way home, but I'm so happy.
你相信吗  我终于可以回我心爱的厨房了
Can you believe it? I finally get to run my own kitchen.
噢  你盼了那么久
Oh, you've waited so long.
嘿  菲比  问你个小问题  好
Hey. Hey, Pheebs. Quick question for you. yeah.
布鲁明岱尔的采购助理  穿上这套装如何
How do you think this suit would look on an assistant buyer at Bloomingdale's?
我不知道  这完全取决于她的肤色和...
I don't know. It would totally depend on her coloring and...
你升职了  是的
You got the job! Yes!
你升职了  怎么不告诉我
Oh! You got the job? Why didn't you tell me?
噢  那太好了  我将决定我们商场卖什么
Oh. It's gonna be so great. I'm gonna get to help decide what we sell.
我会拥有独立的办公室和一切
I'm gonna have an office with walls and everything.
我将有墙了
I'm gonna have walls. Aw.
今天是什么好日子喜事连连  我替咱们找到工作了
Is this the day of good news or what? I got us a job.
婚礼招待会
The wedding reception.
哦
Oh.
菲比  我得跟你谈谈这个问题
Um, Phoebe, I kind of need to talk to you about that.
我想是时候从承包伙食行业退出来了
well I-I-I think it might be time for me to take a step back from the catering.
但我们才做了一笔生意啊
But we've only had one job.
我知道  但现在有第二笔了  就像雪球一样越滚越大
I know, but now we have this second one, and it just feels like it's snowballing.
是的  你要说什么
Yeah, what are you saying?
亚历山卓餐厅请我去当主厨
I got offered the head-chef job at Allesandro's.
什么  没什么  你知道为什么  你可以自己干
What? It's okay, 'cause y'know what? You don't really need me for the business.
拜托  你是厨师
You're the cook.
总不能我自己一个开去别人家
Without you, it's just me driving up to people's houses...
带着空盘子就跟人要钱吧
...with empty trays and asking for money.
好
All right.
我会还回所有你投资的钱
But, um, well, I-I-I'll pay you back all the money you invested,
那部货车归你  我要拿来干嘛
And you can keep the van. For what?
我真是不敢相信  我得离开这里
I can't believe this. I gotta get out of here.
菲比  你等等
Phoebe, wait a minute.
我升采购助理了
I'm an assistant buyer!
（中央咖啡厅）
我们先喝点咖啡  养足精神  再重新出发
All right, we'll get a little coffee, get energized, then we'll head back out.
好吧  好
Yeah, all right. Okay.
很好玩嘛  对不对  我们才不需要那个什么"魔法师"的
So we're having fun, right? We don't need that wizard guy.
我们去了几家俱乐部  跟一些陌生人交谈
We hit a couple of clubs, talked to some strangers...
等一下去码头安排坐船的事
...then after this, we'll go down to the docks and see about that boat thing.
我有点精疲力尽了
I'm kind of beat.
其实…
Actually...
我也是
...me too.
你们是真的假的
Are you serious?
真的
Yeah.
感谢老天  我也累坏了
Thank God. I'm exhausted.
你们要咖啡吗
So you guys want coffees?
对  但我今天想早点睡  来一杯低咖啡因的
Yeah, but I don't wanna be up too late, so I'll have a decaf.
对  我也是
Yeah, me too.
我能来杯热水加点柠檬汁吗
Actually, could I get some hot water with a little lemon?
我刚才在那里嗓子都喊哑了  音乐一定要那么大声吗
I strained my voice screaming in there. Does it have to be so loud?
你说什么我一个字也听不到  耳呜得厉害
Oh. I can't hear a word you're saying, my ears are ringing so bad.
幸好我多带了一双袜子  你知道么
Huh. I was glad I brought that extra pair of socks, you know?
拿来当手套用
I used them as mittens.
最后那家店  脏到我不想碰任何东西
I didn't wanna touch a thing in that last place.
真是太可悲了
How sad are we?
对  我知道
Yeah, I know.
你们知道吗  其实一点都不可悲
You know what? We're not sad.
只是我们都不再是21岁了  你们知道
we're just not 21 anymore, you know?
我都已经29岁了  去他的
I'm 29 years old, damn it.
我想坐在舒服的椅子上  看看电视
I wanna sit in a comfortable chair, watch television...
到时间去睡觉
...and go to sleep at a reasonable hour.
没错啊
Yeah.
我喜欢去安静一点的地方  跟朋友聊聊天
Yeah, and I like to hang out in a quiet place where I can talk to my friends.
是呀
Yeah.
而且如果我回家了  来首Kenny G的萨克思曲  然后洗个澡
And so what if I like to go home, throw on some Kenny G, and take a bath?
我们是29岁没错  我们也不是女人
We're 29. We're not women.
噢  你在这
Oh. There you are.
我很高兴你决定听我解释
Hey, I'm glad that you decided to hear me out.
好  你说吧
Okay, I'm hearing.
我想了很多  很多
I've been doing a lot of thinking. A lot.
而且我想出一番你能用上货车做的生意
And, well, I came up with a whole bunch of businesses that you can do with your van.
呣
Okay, um...
你可以去送花  什么
You could be a flower delivery person. What?
或是送面包
Or a bakery delivery person.
送比萨
Pizza?
摩妮卡
Monica.
我写了一堆你能运送的东西
All right, I got a whole bunch of stuff in this area...
但我估计你不是很想作送货外卖的活
...but I'm getting the feeling you don't wanna deliver.
当然不  那好吧
No. Okay.
我猜你不想送…
I'm guessing if you don't wanna deliver...
就更不会去拉货了
...you probably don't wanna pick up stuff either.
对
No.
不如这样吧
You know what?
我们还是做来做承包  真的么  你确定
Let's do the catering business. Really? Are you sure?
对  我答应过你的
Yeah. You know, I-I made a commitment to you.
那会  那会挺有意思的
Know what? Lt'd be fun. Oh, it will be fun.
哦  是的
Oh. Yay! Aw. Oh. Yay! Aw.
那我们来计划喜宴的事  好啊
Okay. Ooh, let's plan the wedding reception. Okay.
喔
Wow.
你还真的用心替我想了好多用货车的办法
You really wanted me to do something with this van.
这样吧  我要你接下那主厨的工作
You know what? I want you to take the chefjob.
真的  对
Really? Yeah.
那是你真心想要做的
That's what you really want.
而且  我不希望让你不快乐
Yeah, I don't wanna be the reason you're unhappy.
那样我也会不高兴
That would make me unhappy.
我更不想让自己不高兴
And I really don't wanna be the reason I'm unhappy.
谢谢你
Thank you.
而且组织一个新的队伍  应该会很好玩
Besides, it might be kind of fun to form the new A-Team.
嗨  林区太太  乔安娜回来了吗
Oh, hi, Mrs. Lynch. Is Joanna in already?
我的天  你还没听说
Oh, my goodness. You haven't heard.
听说什么
Heard what?
乔安娜  昨晚过世了
Joanna passed away last night.
天啊  怎么会这样
Oh, my God. How?
她下班后出了车祸
Well, she was leaving work, and she was hit by a cab.
天啊  我不敢相信
Oh, my God. Oh, I cannot believe it.
我知道  天啊
I know. Oh, God.
喔  天啊
Oh, God. Oh, God.
我没想到你们两个这么好
I didn't realize that you were so close.
对  很  亲密
Yes. So close.
林区太太  我知道对于我们大家来说  现在都很悲伤
Mrs. Lynch, I know that this is an emotional and difficult time for all of us.
但在事发之前  乔安娜没有给你关于什么
But by any chance, did Joanna send any paperwork your way...
任命文件之类的东西
...before it happened?
没有  完全没有
No, nothing.
只盼当初  她晚个几秒钟过街就没事了
Imagine, if she'd just stepped off that curb a few seconds later...
对  差个几秒钟  她就还能跟我们在一起
Oh. Yes, yes, just a few seconds and she'd still be with us.
她没说到采购助理的事
Nothing about an assistant buyer?
真的没有  不好意思  我得走了
No, I'm sorry. I have to go.
早安
Good morning.
苏菲  我猜你还不知道  乔安娜的事
Oh, Sophie, I guess you didn't hear about Joanna.
我当然知道
I sure did.
我很兴奋能邀请到摩妮卡加入我们餐厅
I'm so excited about having Monica come on board with us.
虽然开除艾米里欧主厨  让我觉得非常遗憾
Although I do feel bad about having fired Chef Emilio.
那就像是失去了一个家人
It is like losing a member of the family.
当然  对你们几个来说  真的是失去家人
Of course, that literally is the case for several of you.
东尼  卡洛斯  玛莉…
Tony, Carlos, Marie...
请告诉你们的爸爸  我们有多想他
...please tell your father how much we're going to miss him.
我知道摩妮卡对这家店  有许多很棒的点子
Now, I know that Monica has a lot of great ideas for this place.
当然  你们都看过她那篇评论了
Well, you all read the review. Ha, ha.
所以废话不多说了
So without much further ado...
我在此向各位介绍本店的新主厨
...I present to you our new head chef.
我只想说只要有热情
Um, I just wanna say, uh, that with a pinch of excitement...
肯吃苦  肯合作
...a dash of hard work, and a dollop of cooperation...
我们就可以把餐厅搞得更好…
...we can have the recipe...
你们打算杀我了我吗
Are you going to kill me?